

Rosamund Teng

I NEED A JOB TO FEED MY CATS

Details

singapore

+65 88777708

rsprincess2407@gmail.com

NATIONALITY

Singaporean

Links

https://kittylegacy.github.io/rosweb/ https://github.com/KittyLegacy

Skills

React

C#

.Net Framework

PostgreSQL

PostMan

Figma

HTML/CSS

JavaScript

Java

SpringBoot

Python

ProCreate

Good time management

High Attention to Detail

Resilience

Collaboration & Teamwork

Profile

I am an Ambivert. I strive to do what I call my best in everything I do. I have good working experience as I did not continue my studies after my N levels. In every job that I have held, I have never let my employer nor my teammates and colleagues down. Its all due to my progressive nature, willingness to learn and be a team player kind of character that I always cultivate in all aspects of my work.

Employment History

Software Engineer Analyst (BACKEND Co.Lead), Lexly Health, Singapore

APRIL 2022 - OCTOBER 2022

- Fix and develop Backend API using C# .net framework
- Convert company DB sequential ID to GUID
- · Refectoring of Backend Api
- · Guide new interns
- BackEnd Documenting

Junior Full Stack Developer Trainee, Generation Singapore

JANUARY 2022 - APRIL 2022

UI/UX designning with Figma

Implemented a MVP web application with the following layers:

Frontend: HTML | CSS | JavaScript | Spring Boot

Backend: REST API with Java Persistence: MySQL Database.

Education

Temasek Polytechnic

JANUARY 2022 - MARCH 2022

JR. FullStack Developer

WPLN, British Council, Singapore

SEPTEMBER 2021 - SEPTEMBER 2021

WorkPlace Literacy and Numeracy Assessment Equivalent to O Ivl exam

N levels, Paya Lebar Methodist Girls School, Singapore

JANUARY 2004 - JANUARY 2008

PSLE, Rosyth Primary School, Singapore

JANUARY 1999 - JANUARY 2004